嘿 我们不在 请留言
Hi, we're not here. Leave a message.
Elena 你得和我谈谈
Elena, you gotta talk to me.
打烊了 打烊了
Last call. last call.
为什么她要让我那么痛苦
Why is she such a pain in the ass?
- 抱歉 - 嘿 哥们
- Excuse me. - Hey, pal.
没事儿 没事儿 麻烦再来一杯
It's all right. One more, please.
给其他顾客留一点吧 好吗 Jimmy?
Save some for the other customers, okay?
给我倒!
Pour it!
你没自己开车来吧?
You ain't getting behind the wheel, right?
出租车会载我
There's a cab picking me up.
我看着你的眼睛呢 Gus
I'm looking you in the eye, Gus.
我告诉你 我今晚没开车
I'm telling you, I'm not driving a car tonight.
该死的
Bite me.
嗯 咖啡
Yeah, coffee.
手怎么了?
What's with the hand?
擦伤而已
Just a scratch.
给我些鸡蛋 好吗?
Get me some eggs, will you?
和玉米肉饼?
Can I get a scrapple with that?
你想要什么都可以
You can get anything you want.
天呐
Oh, God!
火线重案组 第二季 第八集 迂回战术
The Wire S02E08 Duck and Cover
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"它们怎么不飞走呢?"  ---Ziggy
瞧瞧他 神气活现
Look at him, all high and mighty.
你不会就这么算了吧?
You ain't gonna let that shit ride, are you?
在他那么对你之后?
After what he did?
换作是我 我会撞烂他的屁股
I'd truck his ass, if it was me.
不过 他挺壮的
He's built kind of solid, though.
Maui才不是呢
Maui ain't all that.
是给衣服撑出来的 Zig
It's the clothes that give him size, Zig.
你这么觉得?
You think?
他就一软蛋 Zig
His ass is candy, Zig.
你才是码头的传奇
You, you're the legend of the docks.
一拳下去 让他人仰马翻 然后再大摇大摆地走开
Truck him with your best punch and then just walk the fuck away.
我已正式接手14起在查的谋杀案
Officially, I've put us on the hook for 14 open homicides.
所以 要么我们一举侦破
So either we bring in a hell of a case...
要么我就真成了Rawls眼里的大白痴
or I'm as big a fool as Col. Rawls thinks I am.
听着有点孤注一掷
That sounded a little desperate.
不完全是
Not entirely.
Lester 向Pearlman小姐 汇报一下我们目前的调查进度
Lester, enlighten Miss Pearlman as to the status of our investigation.
你说过这案子必须牵涉毒品 才能申请监听 对吧?
You said this case needed a drug connect for a wiretap, right?
过来看看这个
Come take a look at this.
这是我们在追踪出问题的集装箱时
That's the DNR log on the phone listed to the warehouse...
发现它所在仓库的电话记录
where we tracked the suspect container.
显示的拨出电话里 联络人包括Petey Dixon
It shows outgoing calls to numbers that connect to Petey Dixon...
"建议乔"Stewart和"麦克白"McArdle
Proposition Joe Stewart, and "White Mike" McArdle...
都是些东区的毒贩
among other traffickers on the East Side.
这也佐证了我们监视到 有已知的毒贩出入那个仓库
Which supports surveillance of known dealers coming and leaving the warehouse.
同时 一些在监视时拍摄的照片 把我们锁定的街头交易
Also, some surveillance shots and matching mug shot photos from Southeast DEU,
和东南区药管局的案底照片对上了
which tie White Mike to street dealers...
正是"麦克白"在街头贩毒
that we've already made controlled buys from.
证据链很完整 可以申请监听仓库电话
Assuming exhaustion, that's one tap on the warehouse phone.
那对卡车司机有什么正当理由?
What's your PC on the truck driver?
Sergei Malatov: 在本地的异乡人 来自乌克兰
Sergei Malatov: resident alien, Ukrainian origin.
在这里没有犯罪史
No criminal history here.
我们从卡车租赁合同上 核实了他的身份
We ID'd him from the contract on the DAC truck rental.
他甚至人品不错地 给了租车公司手机号码
He was nice enough to give the truck rental people his cell number.
手机电话记录显示  那通打进仓库的电话
And phone records show a call placed to the warehouse...
正是Kima目击到他在码头打的
at the time Kima observed him on the docks using the cell phone.
比对电话监控记录...
Checking the DNR log's history...
我们发现从这电话里 打出的另外七次通话时间
we matched seven other calls from that cell phone...
和Talco航运发生集装箱 失踪的日期一致
to dates and times when a container disappeared from a Talco ship.
还有什么吗? 第二个的申请理由有些站不住脚
Anything else? Tap 2 feels a bit thin.
那在Reynolds街1400号的 Nicholas Sobotka如何?
How about Nicholas Sobotka of the 1400th block on Reynolds Street?
跟据线报 Herc和Carver尾随他
On a Cl's information, Herc and Carver followed him...
在Fayette街和毒贩谈完买卖后
from a drug meet along the Fayette Street strip...
回到了他父母家 南Baltimore的排房那
back to his parents' South Baltimore row home.
当我们用那个地址的电话号码
When we ran that phone number from that address...
和仓库电话的监控记录比对后 一无所获
through the DNR at our warehouse, we got nothing.
但当我们和Sergei的电话做对比时
But when we checked it against the cell phone of our friend, Sergei...
我们发现了一些蛛丝马迹
we got a couple of hits.
Sobotka是你们的调查对象 是吗?
Sobotka's your stated target, right?
这是他的一个侄子
This is a nephew,
从表面看 他起码牵涉进了 街头贩毒和走私活动
and from the look of it he's involved in street dealing as much as smuggling.
但眼下 这案子并没有涉及到 很多Frank Sobotka的方面
But right now, this case feels like a lot more than Frank Sobotka.
没有冒犯Stan Valchek的意思
No offense to Stan Valchek.
好吧
Okay.
我承认 你们的理由很充分
I admit, you've got PC.
仓库电话和货车司机的手机 都有涉案嫌疑
On the warehouse phone and on the trucker's cell phone, too.
那你们也没有了其他调查渠道?
Now what have you got for exhaustion?
有可以合作的线人吗?
Any possible informants?
- 码头方面没有 - 没有我们能收买的人
- Nothing on the docks. - No one we can buy weight with.
- 监视呢? - 我们可以到门口...
- Surveillance? - That got us to the front door...
但是没办法进入仓库里面
but it's not gonna get us inside that warehouse.
开始写申请吧 我会给法官打电话
Start typing. I'll call the judge.
火腿起司三明治 一杯冰沙咖啡(冰卡布奇诺)
Ham and cheese sandwich, and one of them Frappuccino drinks.
- 我听说Charles丢了他的腿 - 什么?
- I hear Charles lost his leg. - What?
冰沙咖啡? 那是啥玩意儿
Frappuccino? What the fuck is that?
他就是一软蛋 Zig 冷得才能让他硬起来
He's all pussy, Zig. Cold cock him.
挑了他 Zig 是时候了
Take him, Zig. Now's the time.
谁知道原来这衰仔也有点种
What do you know? The pissant's got some grapes on him.
还有"香蕉"呢
Banana, too.
该死的!
Fucking shit!
- 把我们送上去 - 狗娘养的! 该死的!
- Take us up. - Son of a bitch! God damn it!
我操!
Fuck you!
你这个超级大蠢货! 去死吧 Maui!
You big, stupid, fucking oaf! Fuck you, Maui.
操你妈 你这软骨头
Fuck you. You're the fucking wimp.
不 你才是 Maui!
No, fuck you, Maui!
- 待在那! - 操!
- Stay there. - Fuck you!
该死的!
God damn it!
你们哪个混蛋想帮他下来的
Any of you fucks try to help him down,
就等着上去陪吧
you'll be up there with him.
馊主意!
Bad advice!
你们这些混蛋给我出了馊主意!
You motherfuckers gave me bad advice!
该死
Shit.
你穿的是什么?
What the hell are you wearing?
没人提到特殊待遇嘛
No one mentioned all the perks.
"网棒球"?(写在了Bulk的衣服上)
Lacrosse?
美国最古老的球类运动
怎么 兄弟我就不能拿着手杖跑了?
What, a brother can't run with a stick?
当初Jim Brown在全美大学生运动会上 还是Syracuse大学队的中场呢
Jim Brown was an all-American midfielder at Syracuse.
此人后来成了著名橄榄球运动员
你把自己和Jim Brown相提并论?
You putting yourself beside Jim Brown?
Lester 我只是说...
Lester, I'm just saying....
我以为你生来就穿着条纹
I thought you were born in pinstripes.
队长 我倒是记得 要是专案组被迫
Lieutenant, I was under the impression that when detailed against his will...
到一个荒郊野外 鸟不拉屎的地方 调查贩毒案件
to some backwards-ass,no-count,out-in-the-districts..Iost-ball-in-tall-grass drug investigation..
一个优秀杰出的探员
a veteran police of means and talent...
能随心所欲地穿他爱穿的
can wear whatever the fuck he damn well pleases.
说得好!
Up to a point.
- 射得好 - 谢谢
- Nice shot. - Thank you.
让一个城里的警察翻山越岭到另一个区 真是要了他的命
It's a hell of a thing to take a downtown police and lose him in a cross-town world.
把东西放那边吧
Take that one over there.
我已经开始想家了
I'm homesick already.
你们笑个什么劲
I don't know what you're laughing at.
那就来亲亲我的大屁股吧
You can kiss my ass.
你真该瞧瞧你儿子今天想上演的好戏
You should see what your boy tried to pull today.
作孽的Ziggy
Fucking Ziggy.
- 你在找什么? - 找不到它妈的账单了
- What are you looking for? - Can't find the fucking bills.
每到月末 什么都赶着付账了
End of the month, everything's hanging.
"希腊人"有捎什么活来吗
We got anything for the Greeks?
星期三 Patapsco港口Caspia号
Wednesday, the Caspia over at Patapsco.
明天Nicky会去拿小抄
Nicky'll go get the slips tomorrow.
怪不得我找不到它们
No wonder I couldn't find them.
你把它们当书签了
You use them as bookmarks.
让我来问你个重要的事
Let me ask you something important.
你喜欢假胸吗 我很犹豫
You like fake tits? I can't decide.
到目前为止 我对假胸还没有个明确的态度
Thus far, I'm undecided on fake tits.
我本以为自己对写报告了如指掌了
I thought I knew what paperwork was.
但是看看你们为了听到别人的电话 而打的申请
But what you all go through, to listen to someone else's phone calls....
你们连字都不会拼
You all cannot spell for shit.
会得话哪还甘心当个警察
Would we be police if we could?
这周的轮值法官是谁?
Who's the duty judge this week?
- Vanderwal - 你觉得他会签吗?
- Vanderwal. - You think he'll sign?
没问题 只要你先替他打扫车库
No problem, if you clean his garage first.
或者擦擦他的窗 也许吧
Or wash his windows, maybe.
去它的Vanderwal
Fucking Vanderwal.
擦窗户?
Wash windows?
是的
yeah.
这些是宣誓人吗 Pearlma小姐?
Are these the affiants, Miss Pearlman?
是的 法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
你愿意声明这份宣誓书提供的信息
Are you willing to affirm that the information offered in this affidavit...
就你所知是完全属实的吗?
is entirely true to the best of your knowledge?
是的 法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
- 是的 法官大人 - 绝对的
- Yes, Your Honor. - Absolutely.
上楼 先生们 三楼 卧室后面
Upstairs, gentlemen. Third floor, back bedroom.
装上吊窗
Sash installation.
要是你们能把窗也擦一擦就更好了 谢谢
And then if you can give the windows a wash.... Thank you.
幸亏我参加了警司考试
It's a good thing I took the Sergeant's test.
- 操 我的膝盖 - 对不起
- Fuck, my knee. - Sorry.
- 名字 - 名字是Francis
- First name? - First name: Francis.
请拼写账户上登记的姓氏
Spell the last name on the account.
S-O-B-O-T-K-A
S-O-B-O-T-K-A.
嗯 是的 是公司地址
Yeah, that's it. It's a business address.
- 你被做了标记 - 被标记了?
- You've been flagged. - Flagged?
电脑上这么说的
It says right here on the computer.
是吗? 你开我玩笑吧
Yeah? You're kidding me.
目前我这也查不到更多信息
I don't have any more information on that now.
随便吧 好吧
Whatever, okay.
明天支票就会寄出来 我保证
The check's on its way tomorrow. Cross my heart.
- 好 - 谢谢
- All right - yeah.
"马面" 要是你三个月不付账单 会发生什么事?
Horse, if you don't pay your phone bill for three months, what happens?
停机
No phone.
好吧 可是我的手机费晚交了90天
Okay, so I'm 90 days late on my cell phone,
他们居然不跟我计较...
but they let me go...
我连支票都还没寄出去
even before I mail the check in.
我问了账务中心 你猜这位甜美的女士说什么?
I ask the nice lady in the billing department why that is. You know what she says?
- 我被标记了 - 被标记了?
- I've been flagged. - Flagged?
她说在电脑上我的账户上写着:
She says it's on the computer when my account comes on:
"不要因为没有付款而切断通信"
"Do not disconnect for non-payment."
"被标记" 它妈的是什么意思? 我算啥玩意儿 很特殊吗?
"Flagged," what the fuck is that? What am l, special?
也许你被天使碰了一下
Maybe you been touched by an angel.
告诉过你了 哥们
Told you, B.
风滚草是被风吹着跑的
Tumbleweeds be blowing through this motherfucker.
就像这些瘾君子也走光了
Like the fiends all cleaned themselves up.
不 是那样的 伙计
No, that ain't it, man.
到处都在传
Word is out,
我们这卖的都是垃圾
we just selling dog shit up in here, man.
该死的
Damn.
Pud
Pud,
- 生意怎么样? - 慢得就像穿着拖鞋走路的白人
- how we doing? - Slow as a white man in slippers.
好吧 回见
All right, later.
我们要完了 因为那些邋遢毒虫 在别的地方找到了好货
We dying 'cause these dusty-ass fiends done found the real someplace else.
就是那么回事 哥们
It's that bullshit, man.
你们俩干嘛待在这儿?
You two got a reason to be here?
- 我们在谈生意呢 - 到别处去
- We're just going about our business. - Keep moving.
山寨警察 那身警服哪儿来的? 超市吗?
Fake-ass police. Where he get that uniform at? Kmart?
要是这里有我们的人在 看他还怎么雄赳赳气昂昂的
He wouldn't even be all chest-out if we had some people up in this bitch.
全乱套了 哥们
Shit is fucked up, man.
该死的 小子 今晚喝得真爽
Damn, junior, you had a night.
即使对你这么一个传奇人物来说
Even for a legendary motherfucker like yourself--
别提了
Drop it.
你怎么了 伙计
What is wrong with you, man?
就因为Elena没再给你机会...
'Cause Elena didn't open up the door for your ass...
你就这么萎靡不振了?
you just gonna let all this shit fly out?
得了 Jimmy 开心点
Come on, Jimmy. Lighten up.
过来撞我呀
Come and get me.
那么 你们在给码头案申请监听许可?
So, you guys going for a wiretap on that port case?
狗啊猫啊都去了专案组 却唯独容不下我
They got every swinging dick with a shield on that detail but me.
你嫉妒了 贱货?
You jealous, bitch?
我宁愿回凶案组
I'd rather be back in Homicide.
那我愿意下一秒就取代你
I'd take your place in a heartbeat.
为什么?
Why?
梦见那个溺水的人了?
That floater showing up in your dreams?
不 不只是她
No, it's not just her.
Chesapeake船长:巴尔的摩一档儿童节目的主角
我是说 我是谁 Chesapeake船长吗?
I mean, who am l, Captain Chesapeake?
我得下船 Bunk
I need to get off that boat, Bunk.
我得查案
I need to do a case.
我是说 如果我不能...
I mean, if I'm not gonna....
要是我不够当个...
If I'm no good for....
如果你就这个要求 去找Rawls求情呗
If that's all you want, just go and ask Rawls.
- 他会马上遂你的愿 - 是啊 干嘛不呢
- He'll put you on this straightaway. - Yeah, why wouldn't he?
嗯
Yeah
Jimmy
Ah, jimmy
...之后 我让"马面"到东南警局的停车场
...after which I tell Horse to go down the southeast lot...
开走他能偷的最贵的车子 他办到了
and steal the most expensive thing he can drive, which he does.
我们打包了它 把它送往你能说出名字的每个港口
And we box it up and ship it to every port you can name.
它现在在哪儿
Where is it now?
在新奥尔良和西海岸之间的某处
Somewhere between New Orleans and the West Coast.
你这弟弟干得如何?
How's that for your kid brother?
你说你是要带样东西过来?
You said you were gonna bring something over?
就这个
Just this.
念念
Read it.
- 是什么? - 类似一份确认函
- What is it? - A confirmation letter, like.
你瞧 那个我曾跟你提过的 港口顾问委员会的职缺
You know that labor position on the port advisory board I told you about?
我提名了你 你当上了
I put you up for it. You're on.
我当上了?
I'm on?
自从他们关了干船坞之后 我就离开工会了
I ain't been union since they closed the dry dock.
我怎么可能当上?
How come I'm on?
委员会主席和我有交情
The board chair and me, we got a relationship.
你是说 你买了这个职位
You mean, you greased it.
主席觉得你正合适 如此而已
The chairman, he thought you'd be right for it, is all.
这职位有固定的津贴 每个月有200呢 Lou
There's a stipend comes with it. $200 a month, Lou.
我晚上回家 只想看看场球赛之类的
When I get home at night, I just wanna watch a ball game or something.
我可不想参加什么大会
I'm not up to go to no meetings or anything.
老天爷 Lou 你不必次次都参加
Christ, Lou, you don't gotta go to all the meetings.
偶尔现身一下 让他们知道你还活着
Just show up once in a while, let them know you're alive.
那不适合我
That's not for me.
那什么适合?
What's for you?
那辆停在屋前的破车需要换电池
That shitwagon parked out front needs a battery.
这厨房都已经破了25年没翻修了
Or this kitchen here has been rigged the same way for 25 years.
起码我取之有道
Whatever I got comes straight.
真是高尚啊 大哥
That's real noble, big brother.
不是高尚 是正当
Not noble. Right.
造船厂的工会倒闭了 你就当上殉道士了?
The shipbuilders' local goes belly-up, and that makes you some kind of martyr?
我和你之间的唯一区别就是 你选错了工会
The only difference between me and you... is you picked the wrong union.
那不是唯一的区别
That ain't the only difference.
- 要是你在我这个位置... - 我没有
- If you were in my position-- - I'm not.
实话告诉你 我很高兴不用去做那些选择
To tell you the truth, I'm glad I don't have to make those kind of choices.
过来 小子
Come on, kid.
坐下来
Sit down.
你以前真和我爷爷一起赛鸽子?
You really used to race pigeons with my PePop?
我们那时都兴玩这个
We all did back then.
有回我给荷兰油轮上的一名海员一只
I gave one to a seaman on a Dutch tanker one time.
他在海中央放飞了它
He set her loose in the middle of the ocean.
让人惊讶的是 它居然飞回了Hull大街
Damned if she didn't find her way back to Hull Street.
顺便提一句 你爷爷喝醉的时候
Which, by the way, is more than I can say
我也是对他说的这一句
about your grandfather... when he was in the bag.
它们怎么都不飞走?
How come they don't fly away?
它的翅膀被剪掉了
His wings are clipped.
这只多少钱 Diz先生?
How much for this one, Mr. Diz?
你干嘛不从鸽子开始养起 Zig? 你可以训练鸽子
Why don't you start out with pigeons, Zig? You can train pigeons.
那玩意长虱子
Them things got lice.
老天爷 还会传播瘟疫呢
They bring the plague, for Christ's sake.
多谢 Diz先生
Thanks, Mr. Diz.
我问过了 Rawls对他恨之入骨
I tried. Rawls hates his guts.
有他的理由
With reasons.
但情况是 Jimmy的心快死了
But the thing of it is, Jimmy's dying inside.
不查案子 他就像列无轨列车
He's a train wreck unless he catches a real case.
- 但是个好警察 - 一直如此
- But good police. - Always.
情况是 队长...
The thing of it is, Lieutenant...
当Jimmy McNulty不做警察的时候
Jimmy McNulty, when he ain't policing...
他就是个无可救药的十足酒鬼
he's a picture postcard of a drunken, self-destructive fuck-up.
当他是个警察时...
And when he is policing...
他还是那个混球 但是查起案子来
he's pretty much the same motherfucker. But on a good case,
他是当仁不让
he's running in front of the pack.
也算活得有意义了
That's as close as the man comes to being right.
再去找找Rawls
Go back to Rawls.
这么说我有钱拿?
So I get paid?
是的 会付你钱 但是你拿不到 钱由我们拿
Yeah, you get paid, but you don't get paid. We get paid.
为什么他们给你而不是给我?
Why don't they give you the money and leave me out of it?
因为我们需要一个人充当线人238号
'Cause we need someone to be Confidential lnformant Number 238...
向局里报备 我们把你报上去 就能有钱拿了
registered with the department. We get you registered, we get paid.
- 所以你们要交我的照片上去... - 还有你的社保号码
- So you're gonna send my picture-- - And your social security number.
然后你们扣下他们给我的钱 我却什么都没有
And they give me money which you keep, and I don't get nothing.
因为你有做什么贡献来换这笔钱吗?
Cuz, did you do anything to deserve the money?
你们有吗?
Did you?
是的 我们为案子打开了局面
Yeah, we cracked a fucking case wide open.
我们查到了一个大贩毒的重要线索
We brought back very significant information about a major drug trafficker.
是我们查到的
That's what we did.
但那是你们的工作 不是吗? 你们靠查案拿薪水
But that's your fucking job, right? You get paid a salary for that.
Bernard 你惹毛我搭档了 哥们
Bernard, you're upsetting my partner, man.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
一成
10%.
分我一成 我就不说出去
10% goes to me and I don't tell.
你不会说出去 是因为你老妈和我老妈是姐妹
You don't tell because your ma and my ma are sisters.
所以你不会说出去 Bernard
That's why you don't tell.Bernard
我们甚至不会登记你的真名
We're not even gonna use your real name.
你会以"毛球"登记 一个街头诨名
You'll be registered as Fuzzy Dunlop, a street name.
- "毛球" - 是的 没错
- Fuzzy Dunlop. - yeah. right.
一成
10%.
太好了 现在我和混蛋一家子搅在一起
Wonderful, now I'm in business with the whole fucking family.
又到发薪日了 Zig
It's payday, Zig. Once again.
那么多?
All that?
东西卖疯了 我都来不及给货
We're rolling out there. I can't hand this shit off fast enough.
这车不错
Nice sled you got.
零利息 钱很划算
Zero percent interest. Money's cheap.
"钱很划算"? 啥意思?
"Money's cheap"? What the fuck does that mean?
意思是说是笔好买卖 你这呆瓜
It means I got a good deal, you peckerhead.
你该考虑给自己买辆新车了
You should think of getting some new wheels yourself.
是的 我正有此意
Yeah, I'm gonna do that.
买辆新车 买件新外套
You gonna get a car, you're gonna need some jack.
还是担心你自己吧
Worry about yourself.
我听说你找Maui单挑了
I heard you took on Maui.
那小子欠教训
Boy needed to get schooled.
怎么 你现在当起流氓了?
What are you, some kind of badass now?
- 是的 是我 - Niko 一切顺利吗?
- Yeah, it's me. - Niko, things okay?
- 棒极了 - 如果你需要更多 找Sergei
- Things are going great. - If you need more, talk to Sergei.
我很快会来找你
I gotta see you soon.
- 我待会儿给你电话 好吗? - 好的
- I'll call you back in a few, all right? - okay.
是那个男人吗?
Is that the man?
- 你不必为操心... - 我要见他
- You don't have to concern yourself-- - I wanna meet him.
让我来处理生意 我是说 你也拿到钱了 对吧
Let me handle the business. I mean, you're getting paid, right?
去你的! 我要自己干!
Fuck you! I'll play the game for myself.
- 收好钱 Zig - 你觉得我做不到?
- Take the money, Zig. - You don't think I can do it?
拿上它妈的钱 Ziggy
Pick up the fucking money, Ziggy.
我不要 你自己收着吧
I don't want it. You pick it up.
你
You.
我操
Fuck you.
我想问问我订的那些按摩沙发 它们送来了吗?
I was wondering about the La-Z-Boy chairs I ordered. They come in yet?
- 你订了多少? - 三个
- How many you ordered? - That'd be three.
货到了
Your order's in.
- 喂 - 我是Nick
- Yes? - It's Nick.
你好吗?
How's it going?
我想待会儿细谈 告诉我个地址和时间
I'm ready to talk about more, okay? Youjust say where and when.
我再打给你
I'll call you back.
没有Barksdale的人那么谨慎
Not as careful as Barksdale's people were.
这里不是西区
This ain't West Baltimore.
他们这么打电话 是因为没料到会被我们听到
They are on their phones because they don't expect us to be on them.
让我来为你长话短说: 这事没门
Let me shorten this conversation for you: It's never gonna happen.
McNulty想加入 我正好用上
McNulty goes after it. I could use someone like him.
我还想要我老二再长个三寸 没门
And I could use three more inches of meat. It ain't gonna happen.
你见过狗闻到后院埋了骨头的反应吗?
You ever see how a dog gets when he smells a bone buried in the yard?
是的 我还见过在我地毯上拉屎的
Yeah, and I seen one take a shit on my carpet, too.
也别跟说他有雄心壮志那一套
And don't give me that he's-got-that-fire- in-the-belly garbage, either.
回答是不行
The answer is no.
你得我对有求必应
What I need from you, I get.
- 不能敷衍了事 不能讨价还价 - 什么?
- No bullshit, no arguments. - What?
当我同意替你去办这些谋杀案时 我也说清楚了我的条件 对吧?
When I agreed to take these murders for you, I made my terms clear, remember?
我需要McNulty加入这个专案组
I need McNulty on this detail.
我的天啊 警督 当我说"任何事"时 我是说...
Jesus, Lieutenant. When I said "anything,"
你可以得到我的一个吻...
I meant I'd let you have a kiss...
摸摸我的胸什么的 你懂吗 但不是这个
feel my tits or something, you know? But not this.
你是想让我破案吧?
You want me to clear those bodies?
我看着你破了它们
See that you do.
他们是谁?
Who they?
也许是从南边流窜来的混混
They might be some CBS boys drifting from down south...
或者是从Edmondson那边来的 Tavon的人马
or might be some of Tavon's crew from over on Edmondson.
大老远跑这儿来?
This far over?
不过我知道一件事
I know one thing, though.
- 什么? - 他们在招徕我们的顾客
- What? - They're serving our customers.
- 水警组 我是Diggins - 我找McNulty
- Marine unit, Diggins. - I'm looking for McNulty.
McNulty 找你的
McNulty, for you.
- 喂 - 我是Daniels...
- yeah. - It's Daniels...
回你的警队
You back to work for us.
谢谢 队长
Thanks, Lieutenant.
线人 编号238 "毛球"
"毛球"?
"Fuzzy dunlop"?
这群新新人类的名字...
This new generation with the names....
一张费用申请单
老天爷 居然要150?
$150? Jesus.
是他使得我们开始查Sobotak的侄子 队长
He turned us onto the Sobotka kid, Lieutenant.
这是案子另一条线 就在这里
This is the other half of the case, right here.
三栋公寓都在六楼 全是出租给Pyramid公司的
Three apartments on the sixth floor, all leased out to Pyramid, lnc...
和拥有毒品仓库的是同一群人
the same people who own the drug warehouse.
这就是那些姑娘待的地方? 还有其他可能吗?
Is this where the girls are staying? Or something more?
不 这栋楼太好了 不会是给她们住宿的
No, the building's too nice for room and board.
这么好的地方应该是为嫖客准备的 让他们更有安全感
A building this nice is for the johns. Makes them feel safer.
那怎么把他们带进去呢? 走大堂吗?
How do they bring them in? The lobby?
- 很可能是车库 - 要么他们有车库的通行证...
- Garage, probably. - Either they have a garage card...
或是被某个有证件的人护送进去
or they're being shuttled in by someone who does.
要是能证明这一点 你们就成了
You get that piece and you're in.
要是控制这些女孩的人 确实和毒贩有关联
If the people running the girls are connected to the ones running the drugs...
那你们可以先端了妓院 然后去监听电话
you can knock off the brothel and then listen in on your wiretaps.
一石二鸟
Tickle the wire like that.
没错
Exactly.
嬉戏的游船 袒胸的女人
Pleasure boats, topless women.
我告诉你 天气要变了
I'm telling you, now the weather's turned,
我得上路了 Diggsy
I gotta roll, Diggsy.
多谢关照
Thanks.
- 从昨天起我们就没拿到过钱 - 还有前天
- We ain't be been paid since yesterday. - And the day before that.
怎么搞的 拜托 伙计 我们的货来了吗?
What the fuck? Come on, dawg, are we back up or what?
货有了 但是卖不动
We up, but we ain't in it.
我们手上的东西搞不过 那些来抢摊头的 所以...
What we got can't stand up to what they moving down the way, so....
天 那我们就得喝西北风了
Boy, we about to dry up and blow away, and shit.
嘿 哥们 我也给不了你们什么
Yo, man, I ain't got nothing for you.
你怎么这样啊
How you gonna act like that?
瞧 我懂你们的心情 但是我还是得让你们走 所以...
Look, I feel you, but I still gotta let you go so....
起码我们可以拿些散伙费吧 对吧?
At least we get some of that separation pay though, right?
哥们 你们最好在我失去耐心之前就消失
Man, you better go on before I lose my composure out this bitch.
这些狗娘养的
These motherfuckers.
散伙费?
Separation pay.
让你的屁股开花吧
Separate your ass.
假设一 那群操纵女孩的人
Assumption number one is the people running the girls...
就是那群毒贩
and the people running the drugs are the same crew.
假设二 那栋楼里的公寓
Assumption number two is that the apartments in that condo...
是那些俄国姑娘的窑子窝
are working as a cathouse with those Russian girls.
这意味这你得找个人 去那卧底调查
Which means you have to get someone in there undercover to make a case.
我认为我们需要一个更机灵的
I'm thinking we need a more subtle touch here.
队长 我愿意为你上刀山下火海
I'd march into hell for you, Lieutenant. You know that.
他看着不像是会付钱的
He doesn't look like he'd have to pay.
Kima?
抱歉 不行 家里会有矛盾
Sorry, no. Domestic issues at home.
我也是
Same for me.
要是被Nadine听去 会在床上阉了我 装进罐头
Nadine would have them in a jar by the side of the bed if she even heard tell of it.
什么?
What?
让西门庆去抓潘金莲
Takes a whore to catch a whore.
它妈的我又干什么了?
What the fuck did I do?
- 给我几杯啤酒 Dolores - 看看这个 哥们
Give me a couple beers, Dolores. Look at this.
我说 看看这个
I say, look at this.
Dolores 是你吗?
Dolores, is that you?
嘿 Dolores 我想为你引见我的律师
hey Dolores, I'd like you to meet my attorney.
这是Steven L. Miles
This is Steven L. Miles.
也许我看不懂这里发生了啥事 但那是它可以
I may not be able to see through all the bullshit in here but he can.
所以 请给我来杯烈酒 也给我的律师来一杯
So, if you will... I'd like a stiff one for myself and one for my counselor.
- 告诉那是假的 - 那就是撒谎了 亲爱的
- Tell me he's a fake. - That'd be lying, hon.
它脖子上挂的是窜真钻吗?
Is they real diamonds around its neck?
你太变态 小子 太变态了
You sick, boy. You just sick.
难道我是南Baltimore唯一一个
Like I'm the only guy in South Baltimore...
想赢得一只家畜芳心的人吗?
that ever tried to win the affections of a farm animal?
话说够了 该干杯了
Enough talk. Now chop-chop.
我要请大家喝一杯 别忘了端给我这毛茸茸的伙计
I'd like one for the house and don't forget to water my fine, feathered friend here.
要是真让这鸭子喝下 那下轮我请
If it's for the duck, the next round is on me.
悠着点
Easy, there.
来个盆子 倒点啤酒 它也要一杯
Put some beer in it. He needs a chaser.
算我头上 Dolores
Put it on my tab, Dolores.
悠着点喝 你今晚可是和一群码头工拼酒呢
Pace yourself. You're drinking with the longshoremen tonight.
你觉得是吗?
That look right to you?
就是这辆车搭载的姑娘 司机也是同一个
Same truck as carried the girls, same mope driving.
那乘客呢?
What about the passenger?
我觉得像
Looks the part to me.
Talco航运的集装箱货船
Container ship on the Talco line,
Caspia号 明天白天到港
name of Caspia, docks tomorrow a.m.
"马面"会接应?
Our man Horseface on it?
我最好给队长打个电话 让他知道我们得布置下行动
I better call the Lieutenant, let him know we gotta set up on this.
不过这一次 我们能监听了
This time, though, we got the wire up.
"眼睛"和"耳朵"都有了
Eyes and ears both.
看来是返程了
There goes the shuttle.
他在等什么?
What's he waiting on?
做足心理准备去圆谎
Getting himself all steeled up to tell some tales.
老婆可以轻松骗过
Lying to the wife's easy.
但直视孩子们的眼睛才是最困难的
It's looking your kid in the eye that's the hard part.
警察!
Police!
让我们看看你的驾照
Let's see your license.
"Robert Johnson" 你相信吗?
"Robert Johnson." You believe that?
Bob 我对你可是很失望啊
Bob, I'm very disappointed in you.
想回家吗 Bob?
Wanna go home, Bob?
好吧 要是一个单身男士 想在这镇上找个年轻辣妹
Okay, suppose a lonely fellow wants to meet a nice young lady in this town.
他该怎么做?
How does he go about it?
他可以打这个电话号码
He'd dial that phone number.
打这电话 还有呢?
Dial the number. What else?
输入那里的四位数
Punch in those four numbers there.
- 然后呢? - 找Eve
- And? - Ask for Eve.
- 什么? - 找Eve
- What? - Ask for Eve.
走吧 回家吧
Go on, go home.
一路顺风 Bob
Godspeed, Bob.
- "Johnson" - 我进"舞会"的"门票"
- Johnson. - My ticket to the dance.
来了 出现了一个
Here we go. We got one.
12-14  Kima
12-14, Kima.
我们发现一个集装箱消失在拖车上
We got a disappeared can just hit the chassis.
收到 我会监视它去出口
Affirmative. I'll eyeball it to the gate.
- 注意通知另一组 - 好的
- Raise our boys. - Right.
Kima乔装的是什么?
What's Kima rolling as?
电气公司
Gas and electric.
喂?
Yes?
一切顺利 你现在来吗?
Everything's good. You coming in now?
好
Yes.
一辆白色大卡载着一个 红色集装箱朝你们方向开去
White DAC truck coming at you pulling a red can.
序列号: XWB
Serial Number: X-W-B, as in "boy"...
C-1-5-7-7-2-6-8
C-1-5-7-7-2-6-8.
司机是一个棕发白人 收到了吗?
Driver: white male with brown hair. Copy?
收到
Copy.
他一通过大门 我就离开
I'm out of this as soon as he clears the gate.
这小货车眼下太扎眼了
The van has too much profile on it right now.
收到 交给我们
Copy that, too. We're up.
- 封条开了? - 嘿 Frank
- Broken seal? - Hey, Frank.
少了什么?
What's missing?
说不上来 一车的尿片而已
Nothing so as we can tell. Can's full of diapers.
- 尿片? - 一次性尿片 是的
- Diapers? - Disposables, yeah.
我想就算是你们 也不会来偷帮宝适吧?
I'm thinking not even your crew would steal Pampers off the dock, right?
这我可不打包票
I'm not so sure.
也许海关的封条 是在卸货的时候弄坏的
Customs seal probably just broke on the offload, is all.
Bea Russell什么时候 从Fairfield码头回来啊?
When's Bea Russell coming back from the Fairfield piers?
谁 Beadie? 她没去Fairfield啊
Who, Beadie? She's not down Fairfield.
别担心 Frank 你的姑娘很快会回来的
Don't you worry, Frank. Your girl will be back soon enough.
是吗?
Yeah?
她在专案组呢 和市里的警察一起查案
She's detailed. Something to do with city police.
好了 我们跟上
All right, we're up.
我撤了 对方已经进入你们的视线
I'm out. You have the eyeball.
12-08 收到
12-08, copy that.
首先是我的手机账单有异常
First I got this thing on my phone bill.
现在我听到Bea Russell 其实在和真警察查案
Now I hear Bea Russell's doing some shit with real police.
- 你是在疑神疑鬼 Frank - 那她干嘛要撒谎?
- You're paranoid, Frank. - Why would she lie?
我怎么知道
Shit if I know.
今天"希腊人"有两批货 对吧?
The Greek has two today, right?
Boris一小时内会回来
Boris comes back in an hour.
第二个箱子在我过去卸的时候 已经下船了
The second can's in a lower bay ready to offload when I get to it.
把那箱子登记上去 你听到了吗
Check that can through straight up. You got it?
和别的一样 把它输入电脑
Enter it on the computer, like any other.
它后面的那个 让它消失
The next can after it, make that one disappear.
- 你想让我弄掉一个干净的箱子? - 然后再发给俄国人 是的
- You want me to lose a clean can? - And give it to the Russian, yeah.
你打算告诉他们吗?
You gonna tell them?
如果是我疯了 那明天我会冷静下来 再把那个箱子偷运出码头
If I'm going nuts, I'll calm down tomorrow. We'll slip the hot can off the pier.
但要是我没搞错 他们会谢我的
If I'm right about this, they'll thank me.
还有 "马面" 堆货的时候确认一下 那箱子里有没有活物
And, Horse, make sure nobody's living in that can when you stack it.
知道了 知道了
I know.
我们这里又有发现
We got something here.
又有一个集装箱在装车的时候消失了
Another disappeared can just hit the chassis.
真是一前一后啊
They're running them out in tandem.
- 那意味着"一个接着一个" Jimmy - 我知道那是什么意思
- That means "one after the other," Jimmy. - I know what it means.
- 12-08 - 12-08
12-08.
Carver 你的那辆卡车是什么情况
Carver, what's the status of your truck?
把集装箱留在仓库又开走了
Left the can at the warehouse and rolled out.
你想让我们盯着卡车还是柜子?
You want us on the truck or the can?
- 柜子 - 收到
- The can. - Copy.
- 我在码头没有眼线了 - Kima呢?
- I got no eyes at the port. - Kima?
- 她撤了 - 我去
- She pulled up. - I got it.
但是卡车已经开走了 你追不上了
But the truck already left. You won't make it.
我给港口管理局打电话 拖住卡车
I'll call the MPA, delay the truck.
打吧 你还在这干嘛?
Do it. You're still here?
漂亮
Good call.
驾照和登记证 谢谢
License and registration, please.
你在限速20码的地方开到了24码
You were doing 24 mph in a 20 mph zone.
你拦一辆才开到24码的车?
You stop for 24 mph?
驾照和登记证
License and registration.
老天 我真希望我们对港口办公室的 电话也有监听
Christ, I wish we had a tap on the port office phone.
我只是想先提醒你一下
I just wanted to give you a heads up.
我们最后送出的那个 是错的
That last little item we sent out, it's wrong.
我放它走的时候已经知道是错的了
I knew it was wrong when I let it go.
别在电话里说 Frank
Not on the phone, Frank.
好吧
Okay,
但是这一次 他必须到场
but this time he needs to be there.
实际上 他肯定想亲耳听一听这整件事
In fact, he wants to be there to hear this shit.
继续 打开它
Go ahead, open it.
芭比娃娃
Bobbie Dolls.
这它妈的是啥破烂?!
What the fuck is this bullshit?
我等的是俄罗斯伏特加 你却给我来自台湾的垃圾
I am waiting for Russian vodka and you bring me trash from Taiwan.
给我你的电话 该死的波兰佬
Give me your phone. Fucking Polacks.
他们是小偷还是蠢货?
Are they thieves or are they stupid?
他在打同一个电话
He's dialing the same number.
东西来了 但不对 一箱子垃圾
It came, but it's nothing.It's bullshit.
是吗
我料到了
I was expecting this.
丢了它吧
Just get rid of it.
丢在哪儿?
Get rid of it where?
蠢啊你 就它妈的丢在街上呗
Drop it in the fucking street.
- 这太棒了 - 是老板
- This is sweet. - The boss man.
被我们找到了
And we're on him.
- 早上七点? - 伙计 你它妈的怎么不明白
- 7 a.m.? - Man, what the fuck do you think?
他们到之前 我们就得就位
We gotta be there, in place, when they come on.
太早了吧
Shit is early.
你们不想干了是吧?
Y'all down for this?
因为我可以再找群混蛋给我撩把子
'Cause I can find me some motherfuckers to swing bats for me if I have to.
你之前可没说要带家伙 好吧
You didn't say nothing about no bats. All right.
那就是我说的 也带上你的小弟 七点
That's the fuck I'm talking about. Bring your boys, too. 7:00.
- 嘿 Poot - 嘿 Poot
- Hey, Poot. - Yo, Poot.
拜托 伙计
Come on, man.
该死的 你这个死色鬼
God damn, you're a pussy-crazed motherfucker.
兄弟不能看女人吗?
A nigger can't look at a female?
可以啊 可是你看一眼 魂就掉了
Yeah, but you be getting dizzy behind that shit.
- 起码我有甜头尝 - 我也会啊
- At least I be getting some. - Well, I be getting some, too.
但是我不会成天就想着它
But I don't make it my everything.
队长 还在吗?
Lieutenant, you still up?
我在
I'm here.
我还守着那第二个柜子 但是没道理啊
I'm still on this second can, but it doesn't make sense.
他把东西运到了东边一家电器行
He went to ground at an appliance store off Eastern.
现在又把它扔了
Now he's dumping it.
知道了 回来吧
10-4.Come home.
你不想监视那柜子了?
You don't wanna sit on the can?
不用了 箱子是干净的
Negative. The can is clean.
我不知道 Frank叔叔
I don't know, Uncle Frank.
也许你是想错了
Putting two and two together, and coming up with six, maybe.
也许
Maybe.
不过 你还是给Spiros打了电话 对吧?
You called Spiros still, right?
Spiros会知道怎么做
Spiros will know what to do.
明天早点过来 我明天第一件事就是去餐馆
Come past early tomorrow. I wanna get down the diner first thing.
好的
All right.
我跟不上它
I can't keep up with him.
那鸭子是怎么回事?
What's with the duck?
Ziggy
Ziggy.
Daniels在吗?
Is Daniels around?
没有
No.
第二个集装箱怎么了?
What's the deal with can number two?
没有走私货
No contraband.
听到他们在电话里抱怨了
Heard them complaining about it on the wire.
有人弄错了
Somebody fucked up.
事实上
The fact is,
他们甚至为这事打给了老板
they even called the boss man about it.
今天收获不错 你们打算去喝一杯吗?
That's a good day. You guys going for a taste?
不 我要把报告赶出来
No, I'm gonna chase the paperwork.
我得去解放保姆
I gotta spring the sitter.
但是如果能送我回家 我愿意灌它一杯
But for a ride home, I'll go for a quick beer.
但是超过一杯 我就会犯困了
But more than one, I get sleepy.
嗯 我也是
Yeah, me, too.
怎么 你没车?
What, you short a car?
需要换刹车
Need new brake pads.
两个 都是男孩
Two. Boys.
你呢?
How about you?
一个男孩 一个女孩
Boy and a girl.
你的丈夫 他...
And your husband, he....
我知道不管我的事 不过他去世了还是怎么?
None of my business, I know, but did he die or something?
你是说除非他翘了 否则不会丢下我这样一个大美人?
You mean 'cause no one would leave a beauty like me unless he kicked?
我只是问问
I was just asking.
他抛弃了我
He left me.
抛弃了我们
Left us.
拿着行礼 去了南方
Picked up, moved south.
说要我在工作和他之间选一个
Said it was either my job or him.
说我一心扑在工作上 之类的
That I was neglecting my duties around the house, all that.
说他结婚不是为了给自己煮饭吃
Said that he didn't get married in order to cook his own dinner.
不过 反正他现在也是自己做饭了
Anyway, he's cooking his own dinner now.
你和你妻子呢?
What about with you and your wife?
发生了什么事?
What happened?
她死了
She died.
不用了 Gus 我够了
Not now, Gus. I'm good.
随你便 Jimmy
Whatever you say, Jimmy.
那么 你准备回去了吗?
So, you about ready to go?
当然
Sure.
马上回来 我去打个电话
Be right back. I just gotta make a call.
请输入你的密码
Please enter your code now.
嗨 有什么可以效劳的?
Hi, may I help you?
嗯 我找Eva
Yeah, let me talk to Eve.
- 我是Eva - 我找人
- This is Eve. - I'm looking to connect.
你今晚想约谁?
Would you like a date tonight?
不 不是今晚 几天后我会回这里
No, not tonight. I'm back in town in a couple of nights.
你之前有惠顾过我们吗?
Have you been entertained by us before?
不 我是第一次
No, first time for me.
我们可以按照你的喜好 为你安排
We can arrange whatever you like, whenever you like.
- 好 - 你想找什么样的姑娘?
- yeah. - What kind of a girl are you looking for?
我们有很多可供选择 等你到的时候
We have a variety for you to choose from when you arrive.
你什么时候到?
When are you thinking of coming?
给我一分钟
Just give me a minute.
停下! 离开饼干盒
Stop! Move away from the cookiejar.
漫长的一天
Long day.
是啊 我也是
Yeah, me, too.
谢谢你的酒
Thanks for the beer.
再见
Goodbye.
嘿 伙计们 他们来了
Hey, y'all, they coming.
这些狗娘养的以为自己在看谁啊?
What these motherfuckers think they looking at?
哥们 你没有它妈的傻了吧?
Nigger, you've lost your motherfucking mind.
- 你站在我的地盘上 - 现在是我的了
- You're standing on my real estate. - Mine now.
你休息的时候 我接手了
Took it while you was resting.
你们都来得太晚了
Y'all too late.
瞧 现在我可以放你一马 让你走
Look, I'm gonna let you walk off right now,
否则就另当别论了
or we could do it the other way.
那有谁和你上?
Who you got to do it the other way?
就他们?
Them?
- 你会在睡觉的时候看到我 - 嗯 我知道了
- You gonna see me in your sleep. - Yeah, I know.
没错 继续走 婊子
That's right. Keep walking, bitch.
他们会回来的
They gonna come back.
是啊 就冲我们这样整他们
Yeah. The way we just punked them,
他们一定会
they got to.
他在哪儿?
Where is he?
你可以跟我谈 Frank
You can talk to me, Frank.
- 这次你做不了主 - 我会把你说的告诉他
- This is bigger than you. - I'll tell him what you say.
狗屁 走了 Nick
Bullshit. Come on, Nick.
那就是"希腊人"? 那个老家伙? 我之前就在这里见过他
That's the Greek? That old guy? I seen him in here before.
请坐
Have a seat.
我们很久没见面了 Frank
A long time since we talk, Frank.
- 咖啡还是什么? - 不用了
- Coffee, something? - We're good.
你在想什么?
What's on your mind?
它妈的每一件事
Every goddamn thing.
首先 我想我的手机号码被做了标记
For one, I think my cell phone's being tapped.
突然之间 电话公司不在乎 我有没有付话费了
All of a sudden, the phone company don't care if I pay my bills anymore.
同事 我听说一个普通的港口警察 就是发现你们姑娘的那个
Meantime, I hear that our regular port cop, the one that found your girls...
在和市警一起搞什么特殊调查
got pulled off to work some special thing with the city police.
所以你调换了集装箱
So you switched the can.
我测试了一下 我给了你一个干净的 把你的货放进仓库
I ran a test. I gave you that clean one, put yours in the stacks.
立刻 港口警察就拦下了俄罗斯的人卡车...
Straight away, the MPA cops stop that Russian's truck...
就在他装货之后
right after he picked it up.
我觉得有人进入了我们的电脑
I think someone's got a line into our computer.
非常聪明
Very smart.
你打来电话之后 我就关掉了仓库
As soon as you called, I shut down the warehouse.
没事 不过现在我们要重开仓库
That's fine. But now we're going to have to open the warehouse again.
再弄丢一些干净的柜子 把它们送到那里
Lose a few more clean cans, deliver them there.
如果有人在监视 正好给他们看看我们没什么好藏的
If someone's watching, show them we have nothing to hide.
但我们的提成还是照给 对吧?
Our cut stays the same though, right?
你开玩笑吧?
You kidding?
你叫什么?
What's your name?
- Nick - Sobotka
- Nick. - Sobotka.
这是个不错的问题 Nico
That's a fair question, Niko.
但是每个人都一样 不工作就没薪水
But it has to be the same for everyone: no work, no pay.
但是不管那箱子装的是什么 我们还是要让它们通过检查
Doesn't matter what's in the cans. We still gotta check them through.
那就是工作 不是吗?
That's work, isn't it?
- 唇亡齿寒 - 你不明白...
- We take gas, so do you. - You don't understand--
我完全明白 这不是爱心奉献
I understand completely. No one is in this for love.
不只是关系到钱
It ain't just the money.
我现在有急事
I got things happening right now.
我工会的事 就是眼下!
Things with my union. Right now!
从现在开始 只剩不到一个月
Not a fucking month from now,
立法会会期就要过去了! 现在!
when the legislative session is history. Now!
好吧
Okay.
我们还是付你们钱
We pay you still.
我是考虑到我们未来的合作...
I'm thinking of all the business we do in the future...
我希望这能让你开心
and I want you should be happy.
谢谢
Thanks.
这是新世界了 Frank
It's a new world, Frank.
你该去花钱买些你能享受的东西
You should go out and spend some of the money on something you can touch:
新车 新外套
a new car, a new coat.
这就是我们每天早上起来的原因 不是吗?
It's why we get up in the morning, right?